<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="no_devices_title">[Ñö Çĥŕöméçåšţš ƒöûñð one two three]</string>
    <string name="no_devices_text1">"[Çöññéçţ Çĥŕöméçåšţ ţö ýöûŕ ŢV'š ĤÐMÎ þöŕţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="no_devices_text2">[Çöññéçţ ţĥé ÛŠБ þöŵéŕ ţö ţĥé ŢV öŕ ÛŠБ þöŵéŕ åðåþţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="no_devices_text3">[Måķé šûŕé ýöûŕ þĥöñé/ţåбļéţ åñð Çĥŕöméçåšţ åŕé öñ ţĥé šåmé Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="no_devices_text4">[Måķé šûŕé ýöûŕ ŢV îš þöŵéŕéð öñ, åñð ţĥé çöŕŕéçţ îñþûţ îš šéļéçţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="no_audio_devices_text1">[Éñšûŕé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö îš þļûĝĝéð îñţö å ŵåļļ šöçķéţ öŕ ÛŠБ þöŕţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="no_audio_devices_text2">[Måķé šûŕé ýöûŕ þĥöñé/ţåбļéţ åñð Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö åŕé öñ ţĥé šåmé Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="no_audio_devices_text3">[Måķé šûŕé ýöûŕ šþéåķéŕ îš þöŵéŕéð öñ åñð ţĥé çöŕŕéçţ îñþûţ îš šéļéçţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="number_one">[1. one]</string>
    <string name="number_two">[2. one]</string>
    <string name="number_three">[3. one]</string>
    <string name="number_four">[4. one]</string>
    <string name="no_devices_splash_header">"[Ļéţ'š šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ öŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö¡ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]"</string>
    <string name="no_devices_splash_subtext">[Šéļéçţ ţĥé ţýþé öƒ Çĥŕöméçåšţ ýöû ŵöûļð ļîķé ţö šéţ ûþ: one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="location_services_dialog">[Ţûŕñ öñ Ļöçåţîöñ Šéŕvîçéš ţö šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ. Ţĥîš åļļöŵš ýöûŕ þĥöñé ţö ðéţéçţ ñéåŕбý ᐅ%2$sᐊ ţĥåţ åŕé ŕéåðý ţö šéţ ûþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
    <string name="add_device">[Åðð ñéŵ ðévîçé one two]</string>
    <string name="terms_title">[Þŕîvåçý åñð ţéŕmš one two three]</string>
    <string name="terms_text">"[Ţĥé Ĝööĝļé Þŕîvåçý Þöļîçý ðéšçŕîбéš ţĥé îñƒöŕmåţîöñ ţĥåţ Ĝööĝļé çöļļéçţš ðûŕîñĝ ýöûŕ šéţ-ûþ åñð ûšé öƒ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. Ýöû çåñ möðîƒý ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ'š þŕîvåçý šéţţîñĝš, šûçĥ åš ŵĥéţĥéŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ šéñðš ûšåĝé ðåţå åñð çŕåšĥ ŕéþöŕţš ţö Ĝööĝļé, åƒţéŕ ýöû ĥåvé šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðévîçé бý åççéššîñĝ ðévîçé šéţţîñĝš îñ ţĥîš åþþ.Бý þŕéššîñĝ 201çÅççéþţ201ð бéļöŵ, ýöû åçķñöŵļéðĝé ţĥåţ ýöû åĝŕéé ţö ţĥé ᐅ%1$sᐊ åñð ᐅ%2$sᐊ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight thirtynine forty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="terms_text_germany">"[Ţĥé Ĝööĝļé Þŕîvåçý Þöļîçý ðéšçŕîбéš ţĥé îñƒöŕmåţîöñ ţĥåţ Ĝööĝļé çöļļéçţš ðûŕîñĝ ýöûŕ šéţ-ûþ åñð ûšé öƒ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. Ýöû çåñ möðîƒý ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ'š þŕîvåçý šéţţîñĝš, šûçĥ åš ŵĥéţĥéŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ šéñðš ûšåĝé ðåţå åñð çŕåšĥ ŕéþöŕţš ţö Ĝööĝļé, åƒţéŕ ýöû ĥåvé šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðévîçé бý åççéššîñĝ ðévîçé šéţţîñĝš îñ ţĥîš åþþ.Бý þŕéššîñĝ 201çÅççéþţ201ð бéļöŵ, ýöû åçķñöŵļéðĝé ţĥåţ ýöû åĝŕéé ţö ţĥé ᐅ%1$sᐊ åñð çöñƒîŕm ţĥåţ ýöû ĥåvé ŕéåð ţĥé ᐅ%2$sᐊ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight thirtynine forty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service_pattern">[Ĝööĝļé Ţéŕmš öƒ Šéŕvîçé one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="dogfood_confidentiality_text">[Ţĥîš ðöĝƒööð véŕšîöñ öƒ Çĥŕöméçåšţ îš îñţéŕñåļ öñļý åñð çöñţåîñš ƒéåţûŕéš ţĥåţ åŕé ñöţ ýéţ ŕéļéåšéð þûбļîçļý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
    <string name="dogfood_confidentiality_title">[Çöñƒîðéñţîåļ one two]</string>
    <string name="dogfood_confidentiality_accept">[ÖĶ, ĝöţ îţ one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_pattern">[Þŕîvåçý Þöļîçý one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_pattern_germany">[Ĝööĝļé Þŕîvåçý Þöļîçý one two three]</string>
    <string name="terms_accept">[Åççéþţ one]</string>
    <string name="terms_decline">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
    <string name="setup_title_enable_wifi">[Éñåбļîñĝ Ŵî-Fî2026 one two three]</string>
    <string name="not_set_up_info">[Ñééðš šéţûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_enable_title">[Ñö Ŵî-Fî ðéţéçţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_enable_message">[Ţûŕñ öñ Ŵî-Fî ţö éšţåбļîšĥ å çöññéçţîöñ ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="wifi_enable_proceed">[Ţûŕñ öñ Ŵî-Fî one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_enable_fail">[Çöûļð ñöţ çöññéçţ ţö Ŵî-Fî. Þļéåšé çĥéçķ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî šéţţîñĝš åñð ŕéţŕý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="no_wifi_title">[Ŵî-Fî ñöţ åvåîļåбļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="menu_discover_help">[Ĥéļþ 0026 ƒééðбåçķ one two three]</string>
    <string name="discover_help_title">"[Ŵĥý ðöéšñ'ţ mý Çĥŕöméçåšţ/Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö åþþéåŕ îñ ţĥîš ļîšţ¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="discover_help_text">"[Þļéåšé véŕîƒý ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ:2022 îš ŵîţĥîñ 20 ƒééţ öƒ ţĥîš ðévîçé2022 îš þöŵéŕéð öñ (vîå ţĥé ÛŠБ çåбļé) åñð ĥåš å ŵĥîţé îñðîçåţöŕ ļîĝĥţ2022 îš öñ ţĥé šåmé Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ åš ţĥîš ðévîçé (îƒ šéţ ûþ)Þļéåšé véŕîƒý ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ:2022 åļļöŵš ñéŵ ðévîçéš ţö ĵöîñÎƒ ýöû šţîļļ ðöñ'ţ šéé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ, ýöû çåñ:2022 ƒåçţöŕý ŕéšéţ - ĥöļð Çĥŕöméçåšţ ŕéšéţ бûţţöñ ðöŵñ ƒöŕ 15 šéçöñðšFöŕ möŕé ĥéļþ vîšîţ: šûþþöŕţ.ĝööĝļé.çöm/çĥŕöméçåšţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight thirtynine forty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen]"</string>
    <string name="developer_mode_toast">[Ðévéļöþéŕ möðé éñåбļéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_learn">[Ļéåŕñ one]</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_backdrop">[Бåçķðŕöþ one]</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_settings">[Šéţţîñĝš one]</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_cast_screen">[Çåšţ šçŕééñ / åûðîö one two three four]</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">[Öþéñ ñåvîĝåţîöñ ðŕåŵéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">[Çļöšé ñåvîĝåţîöñ ðŕåŵéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_settings">[Öþéñ ðévîçé šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="ignore">[Îĝñöŕé one]</string>
    <string name="setup">[Šéţ ûþ one]</string>
    <string name="hidden_device_count">[Îĝñöŕéð ðévîçéš (ᐅ%1$dᐊ) one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="opencast_pin">[ÞÎÑ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_exit_history">[Ðöñé one]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_history_label">[Ĥîšţöŕý ᐅ%1$sᐊ/ᐅ%2$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_backdrop_history">[Éñţéŕ бåçķðŕöþ ĥîšţöŕý one two three]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_backdrop_history_exit">[Éxîţ бåçķðŕöþ ĥîšţöŕý one two three]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_backdrop_history_previous">[Ĝö ţö þŕévîöûš îmåĝé îñ бåçķðŕöþ ĥîšţöŕý one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_backdrop_history_next">[Ĝö ţö ñéxţ îmåĝé îñ бåçķðŕöþ ĥîšţöŕý one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="device_settings_title">[Çĥŕöméçåšţ šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_connect_progress">[Çöññéçţîñĝ ţö ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="device_connect_failed">[Çöûļð ñöţ çöññéçţ ţö ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. Måķé šûŕé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ îš ñéåŕбý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="device_connect_failed_poor_link_title">"[Çåñ'ţ çöññéçţ ţö Çĥŕöméçåšţ one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="device_connect_failed_poor_link">[Måķé šûŕé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ îš ñéåŕбý, åñð çĥéçķ ţĥåţ \"Åûţö ñéţŵöŕķ šŵîţçĥ\" îñ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî šéţţîñĝš îš ţûŕñéð öƒƒ ûñţîļ Çĥŕöméçåšţ šéţûþ îš çömþļéţé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo]</string>
    <string name="device_setup_progress">[Çöññéçţîñĝ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ ţö ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="device_ethernet_setup_progress">[Çöññéçţîñĝ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_configure_wifi_monitor_bad_password">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ çöûļð ñöţ çöññéçţ ţö ᐅ%2$sᐊ - þļéåšé çĥéçķ ýöûŕ þåššŵöŕð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="device_configure_wifi_monitor_bad_ssid">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ çöûļð ñöţ çöññéçţ ţö ᐅ%2$sᐊ - þļéåšé çĥéçķ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ ñåmé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="device_configure_wifi_monitor_bad_ap">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ çöûļð ñöţ çöññéçţ ţö ᐅ%2$sᐊ - çĥéçķ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ŕöûţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="device_configure_wifi_monitor_failure">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ çöûļð ñöţ çöññéçţ ţö ᐅ%2$sᐊ - çĥéçķ ýöûŕ îñþûţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="device_reboot_progress">[Ŕéбööţîñĝ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="settings_saved_toast">[Åþþļîéð šéţţîñĝš çĥåñĝé ţö ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="wifi_different_title">[Çĥåñĝîñĝ Ŵî-Fî Ñéţŵöŕķ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_different_message">[Ţĥé Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķš ƒöŕ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ (ᐅ%2$sᐊ) åñð ţĥîš ðévîçé (ᐅ%1$sᐊ) åŕé ðîƒƒéŕéñţ. Åƒţéŕ šéţûþ ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé çöññéçţéð ţö ᐅ%2$sᐊ šö ýöû çåñ ûšé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]</string>
    <string name="confirm_reboot">[Ŕéбööţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="confirm_reset">[Fåçţöŕý ŕéšéţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ¿ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="reboot_ok">[ÖĶ one]</string>
    <string name="settings_device_label">[ÐÉVÎÇÉ ÎÑFÖ one two]</string>
    <string name="settings_name_label">[Ñåmé one]</string>
    <string name="settings_wifi_label">[Ŵî-Fî one]</string>
    <string name="settings_time_zone_label">[Ţîmé Žöñé one two]</string>
    <string name="settings_time_format_label">[Ţîmé Föŕmåţ one two]</string>
    <string name="settings_locale_label">[Ļåñĝûåĝé one]</string>
    <string name="settings_sounds_label">[ŠÖÛÑÐŠ one]</string>
    <string name="settings_playback_sounds_label">[Þļåýбåçķ šöûñðš one two]</string>
    <string name="settings_playback_sounds_description">[Çåšţ šţåŕţ åñð vöļûmé çĥåñĝéš one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="settings_hdr_label">[Ĥîĝĥ ðýñåmîç ŕåñĝé one two three]</string>
    <string name="settings_hdr_description">[Föŕ ÅVŔš åñð ĤîFî šýšţémš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="settings_privacy_label">[ÞŔÎVÅÇÝ one]</string>
    <string name="settings_opencast_label">[Ĝûéšţ möðé one two]</string>
    <string name="settings_opencast_pin">[ÞÎÑ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two]</string>
    <string name="settings_opencast_getting_pin">[Ĝéţţîñĝ ðévîçé ÞÎÑ2026 one two three]</string>
    <string name="settings_cast_nearby_intro_description">[Ļéţ åñýöñé îñ ţĥé šåmé ŕööm çöññéçţ ţö ýöûŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ ŵîţĥöûţ бéîñĝ öñ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ.Îţ ûšéš å çömбîñåţîöñ öƒ ýöûŕ ᐅ%2$sᐊ ļöçåţîöñ åñð Ŵî-Fî ţö îðéñţîƒý ñéåŕбý ðévîçéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour]</string>
    <string name="settings_cast_nearby_learn_more">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé one two]</string>
    <string name="settings_cast_nearby_learn_title">[Ĥöŵ îţ ŵöŕķš one two]</string>
    <string name="settings_cast_nearby_learn_description">"[Ţö çöññéçţ ţö ýöûŕ ĝûéšţ'š ðévîçé, ýöûŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ ŵîļļ åûţömåţîçåļļý ţŕåñšƒéŕ ţĥé 4 ðîĝîţ ÞÎÑ ûšîñĝ å šĥöŕţ åûðîö ţöñé ýöû çåñ'ţ ĥéåŕ.Îƒ ţĥé åûðîö þåîŕîñĝ ƒåîļš, ýöûŕ ĝûéšţ ŵîļļ бé åšķéð ţö éñţéŕ ţĥé ÞÎÑ. Ţĥé ðévîçé öŵñéŕ çåñ ƒîñð ţĥé ÞÎÑ îñ ţĥé Çĥŕöméçåšţ åþþ.Ýöû çåñ ţûŕñ öƒƒ ţĥîš ƒéåţûŕé åţ åñý ţîmé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven]"</string>
    <string name="settings_information_label">[ÎÑFÖŔMÅŢÎÖÑ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_other_name">[Öţĥéŕ2026 one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_name_title">[Ñéţŵöŕķ ñåmé one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_password_title_setup">[Ŵî-Fî Þåššŵöŕð one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_password_hint">[(ûñçĥåñĝéð) one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_security_title">[Šéçûŕîţý one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_level_description_blank" />
    <string name="wifi_level_description_1">[véŕý ŵéåķ šîĝñåļ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_level_description_2">[ŵéåķ šîĝñåļ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_level_description_3">[šţŕöñĝ šîĝñåļ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_level_description_4">[véŕý šţŕöñĝ šîĝñåļ one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_mac_address_pattern">[MÅÇ åððŕéšš: ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="device_ip_address_pattern">[ÎÞ åððŕéšš: ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="device_build_version_pattern">[Fîŕmŵåŕé véŕšîöñ: ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="device_country_code_pattern">[Çöûñţŕý çöðé: ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="time_format_12_hours">[Ûšé 12-ĥöûŕ ƒöŕmåţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="time_format_24_hours">[Ûšé 24-ĥöûŕ ƒöŕmåţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="time_format_default" />
    <string name="get_info_request_timeout">"[Ŵé'ŕé ûñåбļé ţö çömmûñîçåţé ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. Ýöû måý ñééð ţö ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="execute_requests_failed">[Çöûļð ñöţ çömmûñîçåţé ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="execute_requests_failed_status">[Çöûļð ñöţ çömmûñîçåţé ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ (ᐅ%1$sᐊ). one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="config_wifi_device_not_found">[Çöûļð ñöţ ƒîñð ᐅ%1$sᐊ öñ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ. Þļéåšé çĥéçķ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî šéţţîñĝš.2022 Îƒ ýöû ĥåvé å ðûåļ бåñð (2.4 åñð 5ĜĤž) ŕöûţéŕ - éñšûŕé îţ îš ñöţ îñ ÅÞ îšöļåţîöñ möðé2022 Îƒ ýöûŕ ŕöûţéŕ ĥåš MÅÇ ŵĥîţéļîšţîñĝ éñåбļéð - éñšûŕé îţ åļļöŵš ţĥîš ðévîçé åñð ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ ţö ĵöîñÞļéåšé vîšîţ šûþþöŕţ.ĝööĝļé.çöm/çĥŕöméçåšţ ƒöŕ möŕé ĥéļþ ţŕöûбļéšĥööţîñĝ ţĥîš îššûé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight thirtynine forty one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="menu_reboot">[Ŕéбööţ Çĥŕöméçåšţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="menu_reset">[Fåçţöŕý ŕéšéţ Çĥŕöméçåšţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="menu_feedback">[Šûбmîţ ƒééðбåçķ ŕéþöŕţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="menu_oss_licenses">[Öþéñ šöûŕçé ļîçéñšéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="menu_other_licenses_title">[Öţĥéŕ ļîçéñšéš one two]</string>
    <string name="alert_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
    <string name="alert_ok">[ÖĶ one]</string>
    <string name="alert_yes">[Ýéš one]</string>
    <string name="alert_settings">[Öþéñ Šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="alert_wifi_settings">[Ŵî-Fî šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="alert_dont_show_again">"[Ðöñ'ţ šĥöŵ mé ţĥîš åĝåîñ one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="continue_button_text">[Çöñţîñûé one]</string>
    <string name="menu_offers">[Çĥéçķ ƒöŕ öƒƒéŕš one two]</string>
    <string name="prompt_offers_serial_number">"[Ðö ýöû åĝŕéé ţö šĥåŕé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ'š šéŕîåļ ñûmбéŕ ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé ţö ƒîñð ýöûŕ åvåîļåбļé öƒƒéŕš¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="prompt_offers_button_neg">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
    <string name="prompt_offers_button_pos">[Åĝŕéé one]</string>
    <string name="progress_offers">[Çĥéçķîñĝ ƒöŕ öƒƒéŕš2026 one two three]</string>
    <string name="offers_failure">[Ûñåбļé ţö çĥéçķ ƒöŕ öƒƒéŕš. Þļéåšé éñšûŕé ţĥåţ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ îš šéţ ûþ åñð ŕéåðý ţö çåšţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="device_type_chromecast">[Çĥŕöméçåšţ one two]</string>
    <string name="device_type_chromecast_possessive">"[Çĥŕöméçåšţ'š one two]"</string>
    <string name="device_type_chromecast_plural">[Çĥŕöméçåšţš one two]</string>
    <string name="device_type_chromecast_audio">[Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö one two]</string>
    <string name="device_type_chromecast_audio_possessive">"[Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö'š one two three]"</string>
    <string name="device_type_chromecast_audio_plural">[Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîöš one two three]</string>
    <string name="found_title">[Föûñð ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="configure_title">[Šéţ ûþ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="name_choice_title">[Ñåmé ýöûŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="name_choice_hint">[Éxåmþļé: \"Ļîvîñĝ ŕööm\" one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_enable_opencast_text">[Éñåбļé Ĝûéšţ möðé one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_enable_opencast_description">"[Ţĥîš åļļöŵš ðévîçéš îñ ţĥé šåmé ŕööm ţö çåšţ ŵîţĥöûţ бéîñĝ öñ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ. Îţ ûšéš å çömбîñåţîöñ öƒ ýöûŕ çåšţ ðévîçé'š ļöçåţîöñ åñð Ŵî-Fî ţö ƒîñð ñéåŕбý ðévîçéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour]"</string>
    <string name="apply_wifi_button_text">[Šéţ ñéţŵöŕķ one two]</string>
    <string name="apply_name_button_text">[Šéţ ñåmé one]</string>
    <string name="show_password_text">[Šĥöŵ þåššŵöŕð one two]</string>
    <string name="configure_network_heading_text">[Çöññéçţ Çĥŕöméçåšţ ţö ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="configuration_fail_dialog_title">[Çöññéçţîöñ þŕöбļém ðûŕîñĝ Šéţûþ¡ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="configuration_fail_dialog_message">[Þļéåšé çĥéçķ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ šéţţîñĝš. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="reconfigure_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
    <string name="reconfigure_proceed">[Ţŕý åĝåîñ one two]</string>
    <string name="prompt_friendly_name_title">[Çĥŕöméçåšţ ñåmé one two]</string>
    <string name="prompt_network_title">[Çĥŕöméçåšţ Ŵî-Fî one two]</string>
    <string name="prompt_country_title">[Šéļéçţ ýöûŕ çöûñţŕý one two three]</string>
    <string name="prompt_country_text">[Ŕéqûîŕéð ţö çöŕŕéçţļý çöñƒîĝûŕé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="missing_ssid_message">[Þļéåšé éñţéŕ å ñéţŵöŕķ ŠŠÎÐ. one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="wep_short_password_message">[Ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ þåššŵöŕð mûšţ бé å mîñîmûm öƒ 5 çĥåŕåçţéŕš ļöñĝ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="wpa_short_password_message">[Ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ þåššŵöŕð mûšţ бé å mîñîmûm öƒ 8 çĥåŕåçţéŕš ļöñĝ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="not_supported_network_message">[Ţĥîš Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ îš ñöţ šûþþöŕţéð. Þļéåšé çĥööšé å ŴÉÞ/ŴÞÅ/ŴÞÅ2 šéçûŕéð ñéţŵöŕķ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="restore_wifi_toast">[Šŵîţçĥéð Ŵî-Fî бåçķ ţö ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="wifi_restore_fail">[Çöûļð ñöţ çöññéçţ ţö ᐅ%1$sᐊ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ. Þļéåšé çĥéçķ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî šéţţîñĝš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="settings_network_fail">[Çöûļð ñöţ çöññéçţ ţö ᐅ%1$sᐊ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ. Þļéåšé šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðévîçé åĝåîñ ţö çöñƒîŕm ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ ðéţåîļ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
    <string name="configure_tv_title_text">[Çĥåñĝé îñþûţ öñ ýöûŕ ŢV one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="configure_tv_title_body">[Ŕîĝĥţ Çĥŕöméçåšţ¿ Ļööķ ƒöŕ ţĥîš çöðé öñ ýöûŕ ŢV ţö måķé šûŕé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="noupdate_app_alert_text">[Ţĥîš ƒéåţûŕé îš ñöţ çömþåţîбļé ŵîţĥ ţĥé véŕšîöñ öƒ Åñðŕöîð ýöû ĥåvé îñšţåļļéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="bad_device_message">"[Ŵé çöûļðñ'ţ åûţĥéñţîçåţé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. Þļéåšé vîšîţ šûþþöŕţ.ĝööĝļé.çöm/çĥŕöméçåšţ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ ţŕöûбļéšĥööţîñĝ ţĥîš îššûé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen]"</string>
    <string name="validation_ignore_button">[Þŕöçééð åñýŵåý one two]</string>
    <string name="support_link_pattern">[šûþþöŕţ.ĝööĝļé.çöm/çĥŕöméçåšţ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="encrypt_password_failed">[Ŵé çöûļð ñöţ þŕöçéšš ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî þåŕåméţéŕš. Ýöû måý ñééð ţö ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="pin_confirmed_button">[Î šéé ţĥé çöðé one two three]</string>
    <string name="pin_mismatched_button">"[Î ðöñ'ţ šéé ţĥé çöðé one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="setup_ping_failed">"[Ŵé çöûļð ñöţ çömmûñîçåţé ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. Îţ'š þöššîбļé ţĥåţ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ åñð ðévîçé åŕé çöññéçţéð ţö ñéţŵöŕķš ţĥåţ åŕé ûñåбļé ţö ţåļķ ţö öñé åñöţĥéŕ. Ţĥîš måý ŕéqûîŕé å šmåļļ çĥåñĝé ţö ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ŕöûţéŕ šéţţîñĝš. Ļéåŕñ möŕé ĥéŕé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty]"</string>
    <string name="setup_ping_pattern">[ĥéŕé one]</string>
    <string name="setup_ssdp_scan_failed">"[Ŵé ŵéŕéñ'ţ åбļé ţö ðîšçövéŕ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ öñ ţĥé ñéţŵöŕķ. Ţĥîš måý ŕéqûîŕé å šmåļļ çĥåñĝé ţö ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ŕöûţéŕ šéţţîñĝš. Ļéåŕñ möŕé ĥéŕé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]"</string>
    <string name="setup_ssdp_scan_pattern">[ĥéŕé one]</string>
    <string name="wpa_auth_ieee_8021x">[Šéçûŕéð ŵîţĥ 802.1x ÉÅÞ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="wpa_auth_none_open">[Ûñšéçûŕéð one two]</string>
    <string name="wpa_auth_none_wep">[Šéçûŕéð ŵîţĥ ŴÉÞ one two]</string>
    <string name="wpa_auth_none_wep_shared">[Šéçûŕéð ŵîţĥ ŴÉÞ one two]</string>
    <string name="wpa_auth_unknown" />
    <string name="wpa_auth_wpa_eap">[Šéçûŕéð ŵîţĥ ŴÞÅ one two]</string>
    <string name="wpa_auth_wpa_psk">[Šéçûŕéð ŵîţĥ ŴÞÅ one two]</string>
    <string name="wpa_auth_wpa2_eap">[Šéçûŕéð ŵîţĥ ŴÞÅ2 one two three]</string>
    <string name="wpa_auth_wpa2_psk">[Šéçûŕéð ŵîţĥ ŴÞÅ2 one two three]</string>
    <string name="play_services_old_alert">[Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕvîçéš ñééðš ţö бé ûþðåţéð. Öþéñ Þļåý Šţöŕé åñð çĥéçķ ƒöŕ åvåîļåбļé ûþðåţéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="oss_licenses_title">[Öþéñ šöûŕçé ļîçéñšéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="loading_licenses">[Ŕéţŕîévîñĝ ļîçéñšéš2026 one two three]</string>
    <string name="loading_licenses_failed">[Ŵé çåññöţ ƒéţçĥ ţĥé öþéñ šöûŕçé ļîçéñšéš ƒŕöm ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ åţ ţĥé möméñţ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="send_crash_reports">[Šéñð Çĥŕöméçåšţ ûšåĝé ðåţå åñð çŕåšĥ ŕéþöŕţš ţö Ĝööĝļé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="use_device_id_text">"[Šéñð ţĥîš Çĥŕöméçåšţ'š šéŕîåļ ñûmбéŕ ŵĥéñ çĥéçķîñĝ ƒöŕ ûþðåţéš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="preferences_info_title">[Îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="preference_terms_of_service_title">[Ţéŕmš öƒ šéŕvîçé one two]</string>
    <string name="preference_privacy_policy_title">[Þŕîvåçý þöļîçý one two]</string>
    <string name="preference_open_source_licenses_title">[Öþéñ šöûŕçé ļîçéñšéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="preference_software_version_title">[Šöƒţŵåŕé véŕšîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="help_menu_print">[Þŕîñţ2026 one two]</string>
    <string name="help_menu_view_in_google_play_store">[Vîéŵ îñ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý Šţöŕé one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="mirror_splash_heading">[Mîŕŕöŕ ýöûŕ þĥöñé öŕ ţåбļéţ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="mirror_splash_body">[Çåšţ šçŕééñ / åûðîö éñåбļéš ýöû ţö mîŕŕöŕ åñýţĥîñĝ öñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé ţö ýöûŕ ŢV öŕ šþéåķéŕš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="mirror_button">[Çåšţ šçŕééñ / åûðîö one two three four]</string>
    <string name="disconnect_mirror_button">[Ţåþ ţö ðîšçöññéçţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="disconnect_mirror_button_description">[Ðîšçöññéçţ Çåšţ šçŕééñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="mirror_help_link">[Vîšîţ ĥéļþ çéñţéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="cast_screen_off_status" />
    <string name="cast_screen_on_short_status_no_name">[Çåšţîñĝ šçŕééñ one two]</string>
    <string name="cast_screen_on_long_status_name">[Ñöŵ çåšţîñĝ ţĥîš šçŕééñ ţö ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="cast_screen_on_long_status_no_name">[Ñöŵ çåšţîñĝ ţĥîš šçŕééñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="cast_screen_disconnect_toast">[Ðîšçöññéçţîñĝ2026 one two three]</string>
    <string name="cast_screen_connect_toast">[Çöññéçţîñĝ2026 one two]</string>
    <string name="cast_screen_no_devices">[Ñö çömþåţîбļé Ĝööĝļé Çåšţ ðévîçéš ŵéŕé ƒöûñð öñ ýöûŕ ñéţŵöŕķ.Ţö ļéåŕñ möŕé, ᐅ%1$sᐊ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="cast_screen_no_devices_link">[vîšîţ ţĥé Ĥéļþ Çéñţéŕ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="cast_screen_unapproved_device_warning">[Šçŕééñ Çåšţîñĝ îš ñöţ öþţîmîžéð ƒöŕ ţĥîš ðévîçé; ýöûŕ éxþéŕîéñçé måý våŕý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="cast_screen_enable_wifi_title">[Ţûŕñ öñ Ŵî-Fî¿ one two]</string>
    <string name="cast_screen_enable_wifi_message">[Çåšţîñĝ ýöûŕ šçŕééñ ŕéqûîŕéš å Ŵî-Fî çöññéçţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_settings_entry_point">[Бåçķðŕöþ šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_unlinking_confirmation">[Ŕémövé ýöûŕ бåçķðŕöþ þŕéƒéŕéñçéš ƒŕöm ᐅ%1$sᐊ¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_on_current_network">[Öñ ýöûŕ ñéţŵöŕķ one two]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_on_other_network">[Öñ öţĥéŕ ñéţŵöŕķ one two]</string>
    <string name="photos_setting_turned_off_toast">[Ţûŕñîñĝ öƒƒ \"Ýöûŕ Þĥöţöš\" бéçåûšé ñö åļбûmš ŵéŕé šéļéçţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="weather_activity_title">[Ŵéåţĥéŕ one]</string>
    <string name="weather_search_places">[Åðð ļöçåţîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_added_date">[Åððéð ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_unlink_device_description">[Ûñļîñķ бåçķðŕöþ ðévîçé ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_link_scan_text">[Šçåññîñĝ ƒöŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţš2026 one two three four]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_legal_title">[Бåçķðŕöþ ñééðš ţö: one two three]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_legal_text">"[2022 Ûšé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ'š ļöçåţîöñ ţö ƒîñð ŕéļévåñţ þĥöţöš åñð öţĥéŕ çöñţéñţ.2022 Åļļöŵ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ ţö ûšé ýöûŕ Ĝööĝļé åççöûñţ ţö åççéšš ýöûŕ þĥöţöš, çûšţömîžé бåçķðŕöþ çöñţéñţ, åñð måñåĝé ýöûŕ þŕéƒéŕéñçéš. Ýöû çåñ ŕévîšé ţĥéšé šéţţîñĝš ļåţéŕ ûšîñĝ ţĥîš åþþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour]"</string>
    <string name="backdrop_allow">[Åļļöŵ one]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_unlink_device_accessibility">[Ûñļîñķ ᐅ%1$sᐊ ƒŕöm бåçķðŕöþ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_link_error_all_devices">"[Çåñ'ţ ļîñķ ţö бåçķðŕöþ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]"</string>
    <string name="backdrop_unlink_error_all_devices">"[Çåñ'ţ ûñļîñķ ƒŕöm бåçķðŕöþ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="backdrop_network_error">[Çöûļð ñöţ ļöåð ýöûŕ бåçķðŕöþ šéţţîñĝš. Éñšûŕé ýöû çåñ çöññéçţ ţö ţĥé îñţéŕñéţ åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_device_linking_message">[Åððîñĝ ţö бåçķðŕöþ2026 one two three]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_device_unlinking_message">[Ŕémövîñĝ ýöûŕ бåçķðŕöþ þŕéƒéŕéñçéš2026 one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_device_unlink_success">[Бåçķðŕöþ þŕéƒéŕéñçéš ĥåvé бééñ ŕémövéð one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_device_setting_update_error">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ ñöţîƒý ᐅ%1$sᐊ åбöûţ ûþðåţéð šéţţîñĝš one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="backdrop_settings_turned_off_toast">[Ţûŕñîñĝ öƒƒ ᐅ%1$sᐊ бéçåûšé ñö îţémš ŵéŕé šéļéçţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_setting_defer_loading_error">[Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵŕöñĝ. Ûñåбļé ţö ļöåð šéţţîñĝš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_oauth_callback_error">"[Çåñ'ţ åûţĥéñţîçåţé ýöûŕ åççöûñţ. one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="backdrop_revoke_third_party_error">[Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵŕöñĝ. Ûñåбļé ţö ŕémövé ýöûŕ åççöûñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_facebook_sdk_login_error">[Ûñåбļé ţö çöññéçţ ţö Fåçéбööķ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_revoke_third_party_dialog_title">[Ŕémövé åççöûñţ¿ one two]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_revoke_third_party_dialog_positive_button">[Ŕémövé one]</string>
    <string name="setting_on">[Öñ one]</string>
    <string name="setting_off">[Öƒƒ one]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_checked">[Çĥéçķéð one]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_not_checked">[Ñöţ çĥéçķéð one two]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_no">[Ñö ţĥåñķš one two]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_signin_ok">[Šîĝñ îñ one]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_default_title">[Бåçķðŕöþ îmåĝé one two]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_default_attribution">[Ñö îñƒöŕmåţîöñ åvåîļåбļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="backdrop_ready_to_cast">[Ŕéåðý ţö çåšţ one two]</string>
    <string name="tv_show_description">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ, šéåšöñ ᐅ%2$dᐊ, éþîšöðé ᐅ%3$dᐊ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="spinner_loading_text">[Ļöåðîñĝ ðåţå2026 one two three]</string>
    <string name="remote_devices">[Ļîñķéð бåçķðŕöþ ðévîçéš (ᐅ%1$dᐊ) one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="albums_download_server_error">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ ļöåð ýöûŕ åļбûmš. Ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="albums_download_no_connection_error">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ ļöåð ýöûŕ åļбûmš. Éñšûŕé ýöû çåñ çöññéçţ ţö ţĥé îñţéŕñéţ åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="no_albums_text">[Ýöû ĥåvé ñö åļбûmš îñ ţĥîš åççöûñţ. Çŕéåţé åļбûmš åñð ţĥéý ŵîļļ бé åvåîļåбļé ĥéŕé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="photos_progress_spinner_text">[Ļöåðîñĝ åļбûmš2026 one two three]</string>
    <string name="preview_title">[Þŕévîéŵ one]</string>
    <string name="preview_num_photos">[Fîŕšţ ᐅ%1$dᐊ öƒ ᐅ%2$dᐊ Þĥöţöš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="menu_sorting">[Šöŕţ one]</string>
    <string name="menu_album_refresh">[Ŕéƒŕéšĥ one]</string>
    <string name="remove_weather_location_dialog_body">[Ŵöûļð ýöû ļîķé ţö ðéļéţé ţĥé ŵéåţĥéŕ ļöçåţîöñ ƒöŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="remove_weather_location_dialog_remove">[Ŕémövé one]</string>
    <string name="remove_weather_location_dialog_keep">[Ķééþ one]</string>
    <string name="temperature_format_dialog_title">[Ţémþéŕåţûŕé ƒöŕmåţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="temperature_format_dialog_set">[Šéţ one]</string>
    <string name="temperature_format_dialog_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
    <string name="farenheit">[00Б0F one]</string>
    <string name="celsius">[00Б0Ç one]</string>
    <string name="add_location">[Åðð ļöçåţîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="use_chromecast_location">[Ûšé Çĥŕöméçåšţ ļöçåţîöñš one two three]</string>
    <string name="temperature_format_preference">[Ţémþéŕåţûŕé ƒöŕmåţ þŕéƒéŕéñçé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="location_toast_message">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ îš åļŕéåðý îñ ýöûŕ ļîšţ öƒ ļöçåţîöñš. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="update_prompt">"[Îţ ļööķš ļîķé ţĥéŕé'š å ñéŵéŕ véŕšîöñ öƒ ţĥîš åþþ. Ţĥîš ƒéåţûŕé ŵöñ'ţ ŵöŕķ þŕöþéŕļý ûñļéšš ýöû ûþðåţé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="update_title">[Ûþðåţé Çĥŕöméçåšţ åþþ¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="update_button">[Ûþðåţé one]</string>
    <string name="update_cancel">[Ñö ţĥåñķš one two]</string>
    <string name="whats_on_tab_name">"[Ŵĥåţ'š öñ one two]"</string>
    <string name="my_devices_tab_name">[Ðévîçéš one]</string>
    <string name="get_apps_tab_name">[Ĝéţ åþþš one]</string>
    <string name="open_app_button">[Öþéñ åþþ one]</string>
    <string name="search_hint">[Šéåŕçĥ mövîéš åñð šĥöŵš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="app_install_button">[Îñšţåļļ one]</string>
    <string name="browse_all_apps">[Бŕöŵšé åļļ åþþš one two]</string>
    <string name="view_all_text">[Vîéŵ åļļ one]</string>
    <string name="intent_error">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ öþéñ ţĥé åþþ. one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="trailer">[Ţŕåîļéŕ one]</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_home">[Ĥömé one]</string>
    <string name="unavailable_to_cast">[Ţĥîš çöñţéñţ îš ñöţ åvåîļåбļé ţö çåšţ. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="details_error_msg">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ ļöåð ðéţåîļš ƒöŕ ţĥîš çöñţéñţ. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="browse_view_no_feeds_title">[Ĝö ĝéţ šömé åþþš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="browse_view_no_feeds_message">[Îñšţåļļ šömé çåšţ-éñåбļéð åþþš ţö šţåŕţ çåšţîñĝ ýöûŕ ƒåvöŕîţé çöñţéñţ ţö ýöûŕ ŢV 0026 Šþéåķéŕš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="get_apps">[Ĝéţ åþþš one]</string>
    <string name="browse_view_timeout_title">[Ûñåбļé ţö ŕéåçĥ ñéţŵöŕķ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="browse_view_timeout_message">"[Ŵé'ŕé ûñåбļé ţö éšţåбļîšĥ å ñéţŵöŕķ çöññéçţîöñ. Ţûŕñ öñ Ŵî-Fî, åñð éñšûŕé ýöûŕ ðévîçé îš ñöţ îñ åîŕþļåñé möðé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]"</string>
    <string name="try_again">[Ţŕý åĝåîñ one two]</string>
    <string name="search_no_results_title">[Ñö ŕéšûļţš ƒöûñð one two]</string>
    <string name="search_no_results_description">[Þļéåšé ţŕý šéåŕçĥîñĝ ƒöŕ šöméţĥîñĝ éļšé. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_open_app">[Öþéñ åþþ: ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_clip_duration">[Ðûŕåţîöñ: ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_offer_card">[Öƒƒéŕ çåŕð one two]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_app_card">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ åþþ çåŕð one two three]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_category_card">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ åþþš çåŕð: ᐅ%2$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="redeem_offer">[Ŕéðéém one]</string>
    <string name="offer_terms">[Šĥöŵ ţéŕmš one two]</string>
    <string name="hide_offer">[Ĥîðé one]</string>
    <string name="offer_options">[Öƒƒéŕ öþţîöñš one two]</string>
    <string name="offer_redemption_error">"[Šöŕŕý, ŵé'ŕé ûñåбļé ţö ŕéðéém ţĥîš öƒƒéŕ. Îţ måý åļŕéåðý ĥåvé бééñ ŕéðééméð ƒöŕ ţĥîš ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="found_header_text">"[Ļéţ'š šéţ ûþ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="found_body_text">"[Ýöû'ļļ бé çåšţîñĝ ýöûŕ ƒåvöŕîţé šţûƒƒ îñ ñö ţîmé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]"</string>
    <string name="start_setup_button">[Šéţ ûþ one]</string>
    <string name="setup_before_sound_text">[Ŵé åŕé åбöûţ ţö þļåý å šöûñð ţö ţéšţ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="setup_after_sound_text">[Ðîð ýöûŕ ĥéåŕ ţĥé šöûñð ţĥŕöûĝĥ ýöûŕ šþéåķéŕš¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="setup_play_sound_button">[Þļåý ţéšţ šöûñð one two]</string>
    <string name="setup_heard_sound_button">[Î ĥéåŕð îţ one two]</string>
    <string name="setup_no_sound_button">"[Î ðîðñ'ţ ĥéåŕ îţ one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="setup_help_text">[Måķé šûŕé ýöûŕ šþéåķéŕš åŕé ţûŕñéð öñ åñð ñöţ mûţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="setup_tap_image_text">[(ţåþ ţö þļåý åĝåîñ) one two three four]</string>
    <string name="no_sound_header">[Ñöţ ĥéåŕîñĝ ţĥé šöûñð¿ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="setup_error_steps">[Ţŕý ţĥéšé šţéþš2026 one two three]</string>
    <string name="no_sound_text1">[Éñšûŕé ţĥé åûðîö çåбļé öñ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö îš þļûĝĝéð îñţö ţĥé çöŕŕéçţ îñþûţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="no_sound_text2">[Éñšûŕé ýöûŕ šþéåķéŕ îš þöŵéŕéð öñ åñð ţĥé çöŕŕéçţ îñþûţ îš šéļéçţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="no_sound_text3">[Måķé šûŕé ţĥé vöļûmé öñ ýöûŕ šþéåķéŕ îš ñöţ mûţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="play_sound_again_button">[Þļåý šöûñð åĝåîñ one two]</string>
    <string name="setup_failed_header">"[Šöméţĥîñĝ'š ñöţ ŕîĝĥţ2026 one two three]"</string>
    <string name="audio_setup_failed_text1">"[Ýöû måý ĥåvé åççîðéñţåļļý çöññéçţéð ţö å Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö ţĥåţ'š ñöţ ýöûŕš. Þļéåšé éñšûŕé ţĥåţ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö îš þļûĝĝéð îñ, åñð ýöûŕ šþéåķéŕ îš öñ ţĥé çöŕŕéçţ îñþûţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour]"</string>
    <string name="audio_setup_failed_text2">[Ŵé ŕéçömméñð ñöţ þŕöçééðîñĝ ŵîţĥ šéţţîñĝ ûþ ţĥîš ðévîçé ûñţîļ ýöû çåñ ĥéåŕ ţĥé šöûñð ƒŕöm ýöûŕ šþéåķéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="wrong_pin_header">[Ñöţ šééîñĝ ţĥé çöðé öñ ýöûŕ ŢV¿ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="wrong_pin_text1">[Éñšûŕé ýöûŕ ŢV îš þöŵéŕéð öñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="wrong_pin_text2">[Éñšûŕé ýöûŕ ŢV îš öñ ţĥé ĤÐMÎ îñþûţ ţĥåţ ýöû þļûĝĝéð ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ îñţö. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="done_header_text">"[Ýöû'ŕé ŕéåðý ţö çåšţ¡ one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="done_body_audio_text">[Öþéñ öñé öƒ ýöûŕ Çåšţ-éñåбļéð mûšîç åþþš åñð ţåþ ţĥé Çåšţ бûţţöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="done_body_text">[Öþéñ öñé öƒ ýöûŕ Çåšţ-éñåбļéð åþþš åñð ţåþ ţĥé Çåšţ бûţţöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="done_button">[Бŕöŵšé ýöûŕ Çåšţ åþþš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="setup_failed_text1">"[Ýöû måý ĥåvé åççîðéñţåļļý çöññéçţéð ţö å Çĥŕöméçåšţ ţĥåţ'š ñöţ ýöûŕš. Þļéåšé éñšûŕé ţĥåţ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ îš þļûĝĝéð îñ åñð ýöûŕ ŢV îš šéţ ţö ţĥé ŕîĝĥţ îñþûţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]"</string>
    <string name="setup_failed_text2">[Ŵé ŕéçömméñð ñöţ šéţţîñĝ ûþ ţĥîš Çĥŕöméçåšţ ûñţîļ ýöû çåñ véŕîƒý ţĥé çöðé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="setup_complete_header_text">"[Ŵé'ŕé öñļîñé one two]"</string>
    <string name="setup_complete_check_ota_body_text">[Ĥöļð ţîĝĥţ ŵĥîļé ŵé çĥéçķ ƒöŕ ûþðåţéš. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="ota_wait_percent">[ᐅ%1$dᐊ%% one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_wait_header_text">[Ûþðåţé ŕéqûîŕéð one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_wait_body_text">[Ĥåñĝ öñ ŵĥîļé ŵé ƒéţçĥ ţĥé ûþðåţé. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="chromecast_ota_downloading">[Ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ ûþðåţé one two three]</string>
    <string name="chromecast_ota_updating">[Îñšţåļļîñĝ ûþðåţé, ĥöļð ţîĝĥţ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="chromecast_ota_done">[Ûþðåţé çömþļéţé one two]</string>
    <string name="skip_learn_video_button_text">[Šķîþ one]</string>
    <string name="skip_tutorial_page_button_text">[Šķîþ one]</string>
    <string name="tutorial_next_description">[Ñéxţ one]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_header">[Ûþðåţé îš ţåķîñĝ ļöñĝéŕ ţĥåñ éxþéçţéð one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_options_none">[Ñöñé öƒ ţĥé åбövé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_done_btn">[ÖĶ, ĝöţ îţ one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_troubleshoot_btn">[Ţŕöûбļéšĥööţ one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_download_slow_header">"[Îţ'š ţåķîñĝ ļöñĝéŕ ţĥåñ éxþéçţéð ţö ðöŵñļöåð ţĥé ûþðåţé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="ota_error_download_slow_description">[Ţĥîš måý бé ðûé ţö ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî ŕöûţéŕ šéţţîñĝš öŕ ýöûŕ Îñţéŕñéţ šþééð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_audio_description">[Ţö çĥéçķ ţĥé šţåţûš öƒ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö, ļöçåţé ţĥé ĻÉÐ ļîĝĥţ öñ ţĥé šîðé öƒ ţĥé ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_audio_option_blink_orange">[Бļîñķîñĝ öŕåñĝé one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_audio_option_blink_white">[Бļîñķîñĝ ŵĥîţé one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_audio_option_white">[Šöļîð ŵĥîţé one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_blink_orange_header">[Ûþðåţé îš šţîļļ îñ þŕöĝŕéšš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_blink_orange_description">[Öñçé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö ĥåš ƒîñîšĥéð ûþðåţîñĝ, ţĥé ĻÉÐ ļîĝĥţ ŵîļļ ţûŕñ šöļîð ŵĥîţé.Ŵĥéñ ţĥîš îš ðöñé, ýöû šĥöûļð šéé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö öñ ţĥé Ðévîçéš ţåб öƒ ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ šçŕééñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_blink_white_header">[Ûþðåţé ðîð ñöţ çömþļéţé one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_blink_white_description">[Îţ ļööķš ļîķé šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵŕöñĝ ŵîţĥ ţĥé ûþðåţé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_solid_white_header">[Ûþðåţé çömþļéţéð one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_solid_white_description">[Îţ ļööķš ļîķé ţĥé ûþðåţé çömþļéţéð. Ĥöŵévéŕ, ţĥîš ðévîçé måý бé çöññéçţéð ţö å ðîƒƒéŕéñţ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ ţĥåñ ţĥé Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö.Þļéåšé ţŕý çöññéçţîñĝ ţö ţĥé šåmé Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ åš ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö.Ŵĥéñ ţĥîš îš šûççéššƒûļ, ýöû šĥöûļð šéé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ Åûðîö öñ ţĥé Ðévîçéš ţåб öƒ ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ šçŕééñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_tv_description">[Ļööķ åţ ţĥé ŢV ţö çĥéçķ ţĥé šţåţûš öƒ ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_tv_option_installing">[Šţîļļ îñšţåļļîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_tv_option_ready">[Ŕéåðý ţö çåšţ one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_still_installing_header">[Šţîļļ îñšţåļļîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_still_installing_description">[Öñçé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ ĥåš ƒîñîšĥéð ûþðåţîñĝ, ýöû šĥöûļð šéé ţĥé \"Ŕéåðý ţö çåšţ\" méššåĝé öñ ýöûŕ ŢV.Ŵĥéñ ţĥîš îš ðöñé, ýöû šĥöûļð šéé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ öñ ţĥé Ðévîçéš ţåб öƒ ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ šçŕééñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_ready_to_cast_header">[Ŕéåðý ţö çåšţ one two]</string>
    <string name="ota_error_ready_to_cast_description">[Îţ ļööķš ļîķé ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ ĥåš ƒîñîšĥéð ûþðåţîñĝ åñð îš ŕéåðý ţö çåšţ, ĥöŵévéŕ ýöûŕ þĥöñé öŕ ţåбļéţ måý бé öñ å ðîƒƒéŕéñţ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ.Þļéåšé måķé šûŕé ýöûŕ þĥöñé öŕ ţåбļéţ îš öñ ţĥé šåmé Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ åš ýöûŕ Çĥŕöméçåšţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine]</string>
    <string name="stop_casting_button">[Šţöþ çåšţîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="no_media_info">[Ñö îñƒö åvåîļåбļé one two three]</string>
</resources>
